# **Vincent Patrick Castro**

vincentxpatrick@gmail.com | 0967-296-0756 | Cuatro de Julio St., Santo Niño, Quezon City

#### PROFILE

I am excited to start a fulfilling profession that will allow me to have a significant impact on the technology industry. I am sure that my technical expertise and strong work ethic will help me succeed in a demanding and exciting working setting.

#### **EDUCATION AND HONORS**

**Polytechnic University of the Philippines,** Bachelor of Science in Information Technology 2019 - 2023 *Cum Laude* 

- Dean's Lister A.Y. 2019-2020
- President's Lister A.Y. 2020-2021
- Dean's Lister A.Y. 2021-2022
- Dean's Lister A.Y. 2022-2023

# Nueva Ecija Senior High School, Senior High School

2017 - 2019

• Academic Excellence Award with Honors A.Y. 2018-2019

# Nueva Ecija High School, High School

2013 - 2017

• Academic Excellence Award with Honors A.Y. 2016-2017

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Safe – Midman App

November 2023 – December 2023

Frontend Developer

- Develops user interface for the mobile, and web app
- Implementation of RESTful APIs to perform CRUD operations
- Manual tests the apps

**AHG Lab** March 2023 – June 2023

Frontend Web Development Intern

- Responsible for developing user interface for websites, making the page responsive.
- Implementation of RESTful APIs to perform CRUD operations

# **SKILLS**

- Programming: JavaScript, ReactJS, NextJS, HTML5, CSS/ Tailwind, PHP, Java
- Database Management: SQL, MySQL, SQL SERVER (e.g., create databases/ tables, execute queries)
- **No-code Development:** FlutterFlow

## **PROJECTS**

- Park-King: A Reservation-based and Recommending Parking Mobile Application (2023): This project allows users to book a parking space and pay online. It also suggests other parking areas nearby if the parking lot can no longer accommodate new reservations.
- Beds and Rooms (2023): A property rental system that allows users to view, book a visit, and rent different types of properties.
- Safe Midman App (2023): The app aims to reduce the number of scams experienced by the people. It allows the buyer and seller to have a more secure transaction. The system prohibits the seller from shipping the item if the buyer is not yet paid. On the other hand, the app will hold the buyer's money until the item is delivered.
- Personal Portfolio: <a href="https://portfolio-vixtroo.vercel.app/">https://portfolio-vixtroo.vercel.app/</a>